{
	"questions":
	[
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knight",
			"answer": "Marchog"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Knights",
			"answer": "Marchogion"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knight",
			"answer": "Y Marchog"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Knights",
			"answer": "Y Marchogion"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (M)",
			"answer": "Awdor"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (M)",
			"answer": "Awdoron"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdor"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdoron"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Author (F)",
			"answer": "Awdures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Authors (F)",
			"answer": "Awduresau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Author (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Awdures"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Authors (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Awduresau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (M)",
			"answer": "Athro"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (M)",
			"answer": "Athrawon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Athro"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (M)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawon"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teacher (F)",
			"answer": "Athrawes"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Teachers (F)",
			"answer": "Athrawesau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teacher (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawes"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Teachers (F)",
			"answer": "Yr Athrawesau"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Crow",
			"answer": "Brân"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Crows",
			"answer": "Brain"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Crow",
			"answer": "Y Brân"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Crows",
			"answer": "Y Brain"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Storyteller",
			"answer": "Storïwr"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Storytellers",
			"answer": "Storïwyr"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Storyteller",
			"answer": "Y Storïwr"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Storytellers",
			"answer": "Y Storïwyr"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Dog",
			"answer": "Ci"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Dog",
			"answer": "Y Ci"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Dogs",
			"answer": "Cŵn"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Dogs",
			"answer": "Y Cŵn"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Cat",
			"answer": "Cath"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Cat",
			"answer": "Y Cath"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "Cats",
			"answer": "Cathod"
		},
		{
			"category": "Vocabulary",
			"question": "The Cats",
			"answer": "Y Cathod"
		}
	]
  }
  